"Dear Mom, get well soon"
Tell the head nurse to stay.
Ryoko, Ryoko...
Hello!
I'm sorry.
5:28 PM.
I brought this for Mom.
7 years later
Hey, let's go home.
The waves are too high.
Dad, no luck again?
You don't understand.
I'm only after the big ones.
I prefer real-life girls
to imaginary big fish.
Well...
When you grow up,
you'll understand.
It's called romanticism.
Hello.
I have done the planning.
I'll bring it tomorrow.
Yes... Hello?
Sorry I have to go.
This is too big for us.
We'll share it with Rie.
You don't bring friends home anymore.
Is everything OK?
Did you know that
black sea bream originate as males?
What?
When they reach 15 cm long,
they become unisex.
Then some become female.
Oh really?
What about this one?
We saw ovaries.
Did we?
I don't know very much
about ovaries.
You don't look young anymore.
What?
You look very plain.
Gang.
Hey, Dad, why don't you
get remarried?
Why do you say that?
I just simply think so.
Thanks for the dinner.
It's your turn for the dishes.
It looks like a ceremony for
a religious cult.
They're pretty much the same.
Lonely.
Happy people wouldn't go to
that kind of concert.
The whole of Japan is lonely.
Are you?
You too, right?
Boss.
Mr. Ueno wants to change tomorrow's
meeting from 1:00 to 3:30 pm.
That's okay by me.
I'll be here.
I'll drop in at Starts and
then meet Yoshikawa tonight.
I won't be back at the office.
Any changes and I'll call you
on your cell phone.
Yeah.
Well...
I'm going to marry soon.
Really?
Congratulations.
To whom?
Someone you don't know.
Congratulations anyway.
- You're a busy man.
- It's all right, but...
The profit margins are getting thinner.
How about you?
Don't you know?
The movie industry is profitable.
Really?
I'm lying.
It's like a survival game,
or a game of torture.
- Is it no good?
- Seems like a bright future ahead.
But I don't know how long
we can hang in there.
Yoshikawa. Didn't you say
the same thing a year ago?
Did I?
Awful girls.
No class and stuck up.
Stupid as well.
Where are all the good girls?
Japan is finished.
Let me say...
I intend to get married again.
Well, what made you
decide to do that?
Who's she?
I haven't found her yet.
My son said to me that I look old
and that I should get married again.
That's the story.
You look old...
How are you going to look for one?
An arranged marriage?
No, that's not my style.
I wish there was a very nice woman
hiding somewhere.
What is your ideal woman like?
Preferably young?
Not too young.
She could possibly have a job,
and some training.
Training?
For instance, playing the piano,
singing or dancing.
Your ex-wife Ryoko
was like that.
Certain training gives people
confidence.
A lack of confidence brings
unhappiness.
Pianist.
It'll cost you more.
She need not necessarily be
a professional.
I don't want to fail at marriage
at my age.
I'd like to have enough time
to observe her.
I'd like to see many women
and then choose my ideal one.
What are you laughing at?
Am I expecting too much?
I probably am.
No, I can handle that.
I have an idea.
Have an audition.
It'll be a romantic story.
Remember your documentary?
Love triangle between dancer,
patron and a Down syndrome boy.
Teamed up with a German TV station.
I'll rearrange the story.
Any problems?
I don't see any problems,
but we're going to audition?
Trust me.
Have I ever disappointed you?
Well no, but...
The heroine is supposed to be
in her early 20's to 30.
The conditions are that she be a well
trained person. No problems, huh?
Wouldn't it be fraudulent?
This audition is not only about finding
you a wife. It's part of making a movie.
Collect enough money,
we have the movie.
The story isn't bad.
Well...
Am I supposed to marry
the main girl?
No, a girl with that much talent
wouldn't marry you.
They aren't the marrying type.
Really good ones will always fail
the second interview.
Really?
They are quite attractive.
Smart, with a good upbringing.
Traditional and well trained.
Wishing her to be your son's wife?
I don't get it.
Why can't she get the main part?
They are not unhappy.
Happy people can't act well.
And another thing. I have a plan to
work with FM, I'll combine this.
Make another program called
"Tomorrow's Heroine".
Trust me.
I'm a pro at auditions.
This is Yoshikawa.
I'm in room number 2. Coffee?
Is coffee OK for you?
Bring two coffees please.
I'm in a middle of a traffic jam,
I might be late...
Please hand that tape to
Mr. Kaneda.
Thanks.
Tomorrow's heroine.
I'm just wondering
where you are?
Wonderful things might happen. If you
encourage yourself a little bit more.
Every star has their defining moment.
Hepburn and Julia Roberts.
They led their own lives
prior to becoming heroines.
Tomorrow's heroine is living
at the same time as you are.
No, tomorrow's heroine could
be you yourself.
I'm home.
- Here we go.
- You're home early.
That's right, I've got to work
at home tonight.
Please heat up your dinner.
The bigger dish is for Shigehiko.
- Thanks.
- See you on Monday.
My daughter's here this weekend.
I've got to go shopping.
That's nice.
Hey Gang.
Please put your washing in the basket.
Good bye.
- Thanks.
- Bye.
- Hello.
- It's me.
Yoshikawa. I'm checking
the applications.
They're all good, right?
I don't know what
I'm supposed to do.
It's like buying my first car.
Don't mix your car and wife.
I intend to hold the audition next week.
Choose 30 applicants.
- 30 applicants?
- That's right.
Alright. I'll let you know.
Don't trust pictures.
Composition can be more useful.
Understood.
- See you.
- Bye.
Choose 30 from all of you?
You're home?
Why don't you knock at the door?
You just arrived?
Yeah. Dinner?
I'll eat later. Why don't you eat first?
Alright.
I'm having a guest tonight.
Girlfriend?
Give her my dinner.
Thank you.
What did I do!
Asami Yamazaki.
Classical Ballet for 12 years.
I'm not sure that I can make
an actress of myself.
And you probably won't choose me.
I was simply attracted to this story.
I studied ballet, but damaged
my hips when I was 18.
I was devastated as I intended
to practice in London.
Ballet was my priority.
So my dream collapsed.
It might sound exaggerated,
but it's like accepting death.
Living is another way of
reaching death.
I think I know these facts very well.
That's why I applied for this part.
- When was this dinosaur living?
- About the later Cretaceous period.
The later part of Cretaceous means...
That's a Sauropod, right?
Good. What about the dinosaur
that has the Syracuse model?
- I don't know.
- Do you want to see?
- Hi! Good evening.
- Good evening.
I'm his father.
My name is Misuzu. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I often see her on the train. I thought
she was pretty, so I talked to her.
Good job.
I'm interested in biology.
He showed me his books.
- We ate your dinner.
- Fine.
Was it his?
I'm sorry I ate your meal.
Terribly sorry.
- I will cook something for you.
- Don't worry about it. Take it easy.
Gang.
Good boy.
Let's go for a walk.
Shigehiko, make sure
she gets home alright.
Of course.
OK boy, come on.
Let's go, Gang.
Ready?
Well... I feel like a criminal.
I'm ready.
Let's start.
Pleased to meet you.
Please sit.
My name is Yu Tanaka.
Please have a seat.
- Are you nervous?
- A little bit.
- Sorry, you are the first one.
- That's OK.
We're going to tape you.
But don't worry.
Do you mind if I ask what
your father's job is?
Well... my father's...
job is...
What can I say?
Next one.
I'm going to ask you frankly.
Why did you apply for this part?
Have you ever had sex with
someone you don't like?
Are you interested in drugs?
Can you act a little bit for us?
- Sure.
- Go ahead.
What music do you like?
- Which actress do you like?
- I like Mituko Mori.
Next.
I used to love sports.
At school, I played...
Did you ever want to work for
the sex industry?
I have a friend who is
working in that area.
Next.
What are men to you?
Have you ever seen Tarkovsky's films?
Ren Osugi.
We have some sex scenes.
Can you handle that?
No problem.
Are you psychic?
Next.
May I ask you a question?
Can you smile?
What kind of men
don't you like?
Yoko Sugimura.
Nice to meet you.
If I didn't have confidence
I wouldn't be an actress.
Excuse me.
When I was 2, mother decided
that I'd be an actress.
Can you walk around the chair?
Turn around.
Next please.
Nice meeting you.
It's time for a break
from our schedule.
We're 30 minutes late.
Let's take a 10 minute break.
Sure.
You don't seem too enthusiastic.
Don't tell me you're not
interested anymore.
It's not like that.
Then what?
I'm nervous myself.
I need to use the toilet.
I lived in Paris for 3 years. And have
come back to Tokyo as a designer.
I can't think about anything else
but being an actress.
My office was only for adult videos.
Keep her for another job.
I'm not satisfied being called
a cover girl queen.
This scar is from my first suicide attempt
and this is from the second.
I've been to an asylum 3 times.
Next.
Emi Kitani.
Pleased to meet you.
We finished your interview before.
But I haven't finished
what I have to say.
You have a nice career,
why do you want to be an actress?
I think I've been doing
very well, but...
Sorry.
I'm a children's nurse.
My work is very hard...
Next please.
Ms. Asami Yamazaki.
Please.
- Asami Yamazaki.
- Have a seat.
- Sorry for the delay.
- It's OK.
Have you done any movies
or TV jobs?
I've had many opportunities,
but actually haven't done any.
Do you belong to any agency?
Not really. But I'm on keep
for a record company director.
But we haven't contacted
each other recently.
- Which record company?
- Ace Records.
Could you tell me your
personal contact's name?
Japanese music dept.
Director Shibata.
Since you quit your previous job,
you're unemployed?
How do you manage your daily
expenses? If you don't mind telling us.
I help at a friend's shop.
3 times a week.
What kind of shop?
A small bar in Ginza.
The owner used to be a class mate
in voice training.
If I keep my costs low,
I have no money problems.
Don't you want to lead
a luxurious life?
Too poor isn't good.
But I can afford books and CDs.
That's enough for me.
Can I ask you about ballet?
Certainly.
- You damaged your hips.
- That's correct.
It must have been awful to quit
what you'd been doing.
Yes.
I must sound a bit rude but...
Your writing says that quitting
what you liked...
...is almost similar to accepting death.
I was highly impressed.
I think everybody has
similar experiences.
In your lifetime when you have
something beyond your control.
What can you do but accept it?
I think that's life.
I mean...
I was amazed a young girl like you
understands that.
I think you live your life
in a very thoughtful way.
That's what I thought.
Thank you very much.
Are you finished?
Thank you for coming.
- We may contact you later.
- Yes.
Excuse me.
- May I call the next one?
- Let's have a 15 minute Break.
Fine.
Please tell Mr. Ito I'll be late.
- What do you think?
- She made me very nervous.
I wanted a cigarette.
You decided on her
before the audition.
I like her much more than
her nice writing.
"I think you live your life
in a very thoughtful way."
It's not an interviewer's comment.
I was stunned.
Don't joke about that.
She really impressed me.
I'm sure she's a serious type of girl.
She is better than her photo
and may also be good-hearted.
But I don't like her.
What's wrong with her?
Something chemical.
Can't say exactly what's wrong.
I just don't like her.
Your girlfriend seemed nice.
Misuzu?
- She looked nice, but...
- What?
One of those girl things.
I don't understand girls.
Don't you?
Thanks.
Hey, Dad, about your remarriage.
Preferably someone
who cooks better than Rie.
Why are you in such a hurry?
New discovery of another dinosaur,
from Argentina.
- That one could be older than Euraptile.
- Really.
I'll be busy collecting information.
Take a bath.
Yes, hello.
Sorry for calling so late.
This is producer Aoyama.
I interviewed you today.
- Thank you for your time today.
- Not at all. Well...
I wondered if you might have
some time to talk with me.
Of course. I'd love to see you.
When would be good for you?
Anytime would be fine,
during the daytime.
Really. Let me see.
For instance...
Good night.
This is the Aoyama residence.
- It's me.
- How is it?
About Ms. Yamazaki.
Not that I doubted her,
I called Ace Records.
It's no big deal, but something
didn't seem right.
What is it?
Director Shibata isn't
at the company.
To be precise,
he isn't there anymore.
He's been missing for a year.
He just disappeared.
I'm nervous.
Please relax, I won't ask you
any special questions.
You only ask of me to enjoy
this nice food and talk?
Absolutely.
That's the best request
I've ever had.
Just one question.
Your director contact.
Mr. Shibata?
I'm sorry I said so at the audition, but...
In fact I've never met him.
I don't belong to any actors' agency.
I was advised to answer you like that.
Is that so?
I didn't mean to tell a lie.
It's OK. I've clarified that question,
that's no problem.
Here we go.
Looks wonderful.
Go ahead.
- Yummy.
- Good.
I hope I'm not asking you
too much, and...
You probably can't, but...
If you have some free time...
I'd like to talk to you more.
I don't have anybody to be
frank with.
If I'm good enough,
I'd love to.
Really? I'm very happy about that.
I'll try not to bother you.
I don't mind any place.
Even on the telephone
would be fine.
I'll write my cellular phone number
on my business card.
Please call me anytime.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for the meal too.
I've decided.
I don't care about the movie,
I'm interested only in her.
Don't worry about the movie.
I'll handle that matter.
But don't be too hasty.
You wanted to have some time
to observe your prospect.
Why are you so negative about her?
What's wrong with her?
I only think that
life isn't so easy.
She is beautiful, classy
and obedient.
Such a woman not having
any boyfriends is unthinkable.
I checked out her associates,
none are accessible.
The bar she was talking about
is also an unknown.
We can't reach anybody
who knows her.
I wasn't born yesterday.
I won't be fooled that easily.
I trust myself over some
other's evaluation.
If there's any trouble,
I can solve it.
OK.
You said I could find my ideal woman
from an audition.
I appreciate it.
Hey, Aoyama.
Promise me one thing.
Don't call her.
Hopefully I'm wrong about this, but...
It's going to affect your whole life.
Don't be so hasty.
Cool down a bit.
Alright. I promise you.
You're not sick, are you?
It is rare for you to take a day off.
Since I've worked for you,
I've never seen you like this.
Oh well...
It's good to have a break.
You might be a little tired.
Since your wife died,
you've worked very hard for your son.
Forming your own company,
which is doing quite well.
You work too much.
I wish my husband was like you.
My life would be easier.
You must have a nice girlfriend.
I'm sure you do.
Men can't maintain without
female support.
I've finished.
I'm going home.
- Bye.
- See you tomorrow.
I'm leaving.
See you.
Oh? What is it?
Not really.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
This is Aoyama.
Really?
Good. I thought you wouldn't
phone me anymore.
If I told the truth, you might think
that I'm a heavy woman.
I've been longing for your call.
Sorry.
So how are you?
What?
What's so funny?
I never thought about having a date
with you again. So I'm pretty excited.
Here we go.
I never asked you about your family.
Are they fine?
- They're fine.
- You're from Tokyo, right?
They bought a house in Chiba.
Just moved in last month.
My father loves golf, living
in Chiba is more convenient.
- Really?
- We are not that close.
But not that distant either.
Quite an average family.
- Do you still work at the bar?
- Yes.
Is that in Ginza?
It's on 4th street.
Called the Stone Fish. Funny name.
The Stone Fish?
Shall I come for a drink?
Thank you... but...
...the owner interferes with
my private things.
If you don't want me to come
of course I won't.
I'm just curious about you.
I won't lie to you,
definitely not.
I promise.
I have to tell you...
Can I tell you the truth
about the movie?
- Someone else got the part?
- It's not like that. The movie itself.
Actually the sponsor didn't like
some of the story.
We had to suspend it.
In the worst case it might
not come out.
Oh really?
You might be hurt.
Not me. But you might be.
You read my composition,
didn't you?
I never thought I'd get the main part.
It's OK. The good thing is
that I met you.
I felt wonderful seeing
myself in the mirror.
Joining images of myself
and beautiful things.
That's incredible, I trained
myself hard to release pain.
That's why I could
tolerate hard lessons.
But eventually I lost
my precious ballet.
It's hard to forget about it.
But someday you'll feel
that life is wonderful.
That's life, isn't it?
Thank you.
Living alone is a hassle.
I have nobody to talk with.
There were some guys
that approached me.
But you are the first one
to support me.
Warmly wrapping me and
trying to understand me.
- Let's have dinner soon.
- When will that be?
Sorry. Am I pushing you?
I'll call you.
Yes, I'll wait for you.
Here is fine.
Please stop the car.
She's getting off.
- Thank you very much for today.
- See you.
- Good night.
- Bye.
Take me to Okusawa.
Yes?
- Can I talk to you for a moment?
- What?
Well well, the drapes are dirty.
What?
Well...
You found a girlfriend.
Am I right?
Bingo.
You look a little different,
sometimes you even smile.
She is only 24 years old.
She's closer to my age.
Must be very beautiful.
I'm the same as you.
I like the beautiful ones.
Don't get fooled.
I'm much cleverer than you.
Have you proposed to her?
Not yet.
We are going away this weekend.
I'm going to propose to her then.
Good luck!
I'll introduce her to you soon.
Let me check her out first.
I trust my hunches.
Because you're blind in love now.
Well, what can we do before dinner?
I know the chef here is very good.
He provides very nice food.
But he has a terrible mouth.
There is a little museum close by.
If we leave now,
we could still make it.
It's about 20 minutes By car.
After that, we could go
to the harbour.
It's a little harbour,
but it has a nice coffee shop.
They serve nice cheesecake.
Their desserts are...
Come to me.
Please.
Don't take off your clothes yet.
Please...
Look at my body.
I burnt myself when I was little.
I want you to know all about me.
You are very beautiful.
Please love me.
Only me.
I understand.
Everybody says so.
But I hope you are different
from the others.
Only me.
OK?
Only me. Please love me.
Only me.
Yes.
Is that Mr. Aoyama?
This is the front desk.
Yes.
I'm terribly sorry.
You must be in bed.
We tried calling many times
but there was no answer.
Your partner has left.
We want to confirm your stay.
Sorry to call you so late,
but we need to know.
Left?
What you are saying is
she disappeared?
Nobody answers the phone.
There's no way to contact her.
I don't know exactly
where she lives either.
- What happened in the hotel?
- I told you all about it.
But normally people don't
disappear like that.
We might have misunderstood
each other somehow.
I just want to talk to her
face to face.
Yoshikawa, can you find out
her address?
Aoyama,
I've only got her resume.
It's impossible.
- Why don't you forget about her.
- I can't do that.
I can't finish everything like this.
I know I can't convince you but...
I suggest you forget about her.
You're saying...
...that I...
...went too crazy about
a young girl.
Eventually being left alone
like a pathetic old fart?
Yes, you are.
What's the matter with you? You said
that you weren't born yesterday.
Whatever problems come up,
you fix them, right? Oh come on!
What?
- It's OK.
- What's OK about it?
It's OK now.
I won't ask your help anymore.
I'll look for her.
- I'll look for her myself.
- Aoyama!
"Shimada Ballet Studio"
Excuse me?
Excuse me, but...
Excuse me.
Are you...
Are you Mr. Shimada?
I'm the one who called you
this afternoon.
About Miss Asami Yamazaki.
Go home.
Let me be frank with you.
Did you have any problems
with Asami before?
I just want to know
how to contact her.
And I'm looking for a clue.
Did you see her?
Yes.
Did you hear her voice?
What do you mean by that?
Did you touch her body?
Did you hold her in your arms?
How was that?
Was it good?
Did you smell her?
Asami...
Go home.
4th Street.
The Stone Fish.
"The Stone Fish"
No one is there.
Are you closed today?
That bar closed about a year ago.
That was huge mess.
The owner was murdered.
Do you know an Asami
who used to work here?
Asami? I don't recall.
Normally the owner worked
here alone.
Asami was supposed to be
working here 3 times a week.
Some kind of a mistake.
Excuse me...
Why was the owner killed?
I'm not sure but people talked about
some sort of man problem.
She used to be associated with
a music industry guy.
She used drugs too.
Did she get murdered here?
The body was chopped up completely.
It's a 28 year old building.
The whole thing is tilted.
We saw her blood flowing
through a gap in the door.
The other mystery was...
The police tried to recompose
her body together.
3 extra fingers and
an ear came up.
An extra tongue as well.
Isn't it a terrible world?
Meal time, Gang.
Bye.
Hi, this is Shigehiko.
I'm going to stay at
my friend's house tonight.
It's none of my business,
but eat properly.
There's some yogurt there,
please have it.
And Gang was hiding. Underneath
the house, please feed him.
Talk to you later.
I'm sorry.
How have you been?
I never expected we would meet again.
Sorry to be childish.
I never asked you about your family.
Are they fine?
When I was little,
my parents got a divorce.
I was sent to my uncle's house.
That was a terrible place.
I only remember being abused.
My uncle's wife was
that sort of woman.
I have many scars.
If it's too painful,
you needn't talk about.
No, I want you to know
all about me.
I was forced into cold baths in winter,
and I got pneumonia.
She pushed me down the staircase.
I broke my shoulder bone.
The doctor worried about me.
He sent me back to
my mother's home.
When was that?
I was 7 years old.
Really.
My mother had remarried.
I've reduced the scars.
But my stepfather...
Hated me so much.
He's got disabled legs.
Staying at home all the time.
I did nothing in a dark room everyday.
Until my mother came home.
I'm sorry.
It's not a normal story is it?
If you dislike me,
please say so.
Strange.
I never imagined you'd had
such an agonizing past.
Because ballet supported me.
You had talent.
I'm not sure.
But when I danced,
it purified the dark side of me.
That's the reason why
I never tried to kill myself.
I think... you're wonderful.
I've been looking for
someone like you.
Darling.
Ryoko.
This is an opportune time.
Let me introduce you. This is Asami.
No...
She isn't good for you.
She's a very fine woman.
No... darling, no.
I want...
I want you right now.
Asami.
That was a little mistake.
You made love to me.
Only once.
I expected something from you.
Was I stupid?
Sorry.
Forgive me.
I'll do anything to give
you pleasure.
I like doing this.
What are you doing!
Stop it.
Look, you've got a hard on.
Stop it!
3 extra fingers, an ear...
...and a tongue too.
You only love me.
Only me.
Asami.
Dance for me.
Dance.
Dance, bitch!
Dance...
...for me otherwise...
...I'll torture you!
Dance.
Please.
Dance for me. Dance!
Asami...
Good girl.
Asami!
This wire can...
...cut meat and bone very easily.
You are wonderful.
I never felt unhappy.
Because I've been unhappy
all the time.
- Asami!
- Please stop!
No!
Males need female support.
Otherwise they can't maintain.
Let's have an audition.
My son told me that I look old.
Why don't I remarry.
That's why I decided.
Asami...
You...
You can't move any more.
I've paralyzed your body but
your nerves are still awake.
You can enjoy the pain
and suffer incredibly.
You guys collect many girls
from auditions.
Make them fail.
You contact them later.
Just wanting to have sex.
Everybody is the same.
Deeper, deeper...
Painful?
Words create lies.
Pain can be trusted.
Right?
You can feel pain. You can study
about the human body as well.
Deeper...
This is the most painful point.
Am I right?
Then here too.
Here as well.
Right?
Deeper, deeper...
Here we go. Underneath the
eyes is also very painful.
You only realize what kind
of man you are...
...when you feel pain,
you understand.
When you have a very
agonizing experience.
Your son is called Shigehiko, right?
Your son has to suffer pain,
then you'll understand more.
Stop that!
Stay away from my son.
You love your son, too?
You're a liar.
You only love me, right?
I've only got you.
But you have so many others.
I don't want to be
one of them.
Even if I give you all of me,
you won't be mine completely.
Everybody is the same.
Everybody.
You can't go anywhere
without feet.
This wire can cut
meat and bone easily.
Stop it!
Right foot, please.
I'm home.
Dad, are you awake?
My friend got sick all of a sudden.
So we called an ambulance.
Are you there?
What happened, Dad?
What's going on?
What happened?
Are you OK?
Well...
I will...
I'll answer your proposal.
What?
Your proposal...
I accept.
Proposal?
It's like a dream.
I'm so happy.
I applied for the audition.
I was the...
...luckiest one.
Because I didn't become
the heroine of the movie.
But I became the real heroine.
Deeper, deeper...
What's wrong, Dad?
Who the hell are you?
What the hell do you want?
What's going on?
Dad!
Are you alright, Dad?
Call the police...
Police...
Is this the police? This is the Aoyama
residence, Okusawa.
Please send an ambulance.
My father's been seriously injured.
And one woman too.
I don't know the details.
His left leg has been chopped off
and is bleeding badly.
The address is Okusawa 6-20-4.
I thought you were very busy.
I don't know your job so well.
I might sound heavy.
But I've been waiting for
your call for a long time.
I never expected that
we would meet again.
Sorry to have been childish.
It's a hassle living alone.
I didn't have anybody to talk with.
You are the first one to support me...
Warmly wrapping me...
Trying to understand me...
It's hard to forget about.
But someday you'll feel...
...that life is wonderful.
That's life, isn't it?
Shigeharu Aoyama
RYO ISHIBASHI
Asami Yamazaki
EIHI SHIINA
Shigehiko Aoyama
TETSU SAWAKI
Yasuhisa Yoshikawa
JUN KUNIMURA
Old Man in Wheelchair
RENJI ISHIBASHI
Ryoko Aoyama
MIYUKI MATSUDA
Executive Producer
TOYOYUKI YOKOHAMA
Planner
JUNICHI SHINDO
Produced by
SATOSHI FUKUSHIMA
AKEMI SUYAMA
Based on the novel by
RYU MURAKAMI
Screenplay by
DAISUKE TENGAN
Directed by
TAKASHI MIIKE